// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {
  
  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/en.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: [],

}



export var cards = {
  "a": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>A</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Alfa"
  },
  "b": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>B</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Bravo"
  }, 
  "c": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>C</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Charlie"
  },
  "d": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>D</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Delta"
  },
  "e": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>E</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Echo"
  },
  "f": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>F</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Foxtrot"
  },
  "g": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>G</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Golf"
  },
  "h": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>H</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Hotel"
  },
  "i": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>I</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "India"
  },
  "j": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>J</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Juliett"
  },
  "k": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>K</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Kilo"
  },
  "l": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>L</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Lima"
  },
  "m": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>M</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Mike"
  },
  "n": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>N</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "November"
  },
  "o": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>O</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Oscar"
  },
  "p": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>P</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Papa"
  },
  "q": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>Q</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Quebec"
  },
  "r": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>R</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Romeo"
  },
  "s": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>S</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Sierra"
  },
  "t": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>T</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Tango"
  },
  "u": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>U</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Uniform"
  },
  "v": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>V</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Victor"
  },
  "w": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>W</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Whiskey"
  },
  "x": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>X</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Xray"
  },
  "y": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>Y</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Yankee"
  },
  "z": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Code word for <em>Z</em>?',
    prompt: "Code for this letter?",
    answer: "Zulu"
  },
};